Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publications
  - Bulletins on school architecture & hygiene for the U.S. Office of Education
Columbia School Supply Co. March 16, 191 2
Mandel Brothers March 16, 191 2
Sears, Roebuck & Co. March 16, 191 2
Columbia School Supply Co. March 20, 191 2
Feagin, William F. March 20, 191 2
Hood, C.M. March 20, 191 2
LeGarde, Ellen March 20, 191 2
Ferrell, John A. March 23, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 23, 191 2
Randolph McNutt Co. March 24, 191 2
American Seating Co. April 2, 1914 2
Burton, E.D. April 2, 1914 2
Payne, Bruce R. April 16, 1914 2
Payne, Bruce R. April 20, 1914 2
Ryan, W.C., Jr. April 23, 1914 2
Smith, Meredith April 23, 1914 2
Green, Frederick R. April 28, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 28, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson April 28, 1914 2
Stechert, G.E. April 28, 1914 2
Wood, W.O. April 28, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 29, 1914 2
LeGarde, Ellen April 29, 1914 2
Roach, Walter April 29, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson April 29, 1914 2
Stiles, Charles W. April 29, 1914 2
Stiles, Charles W. April 29, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 30, 1914 2
Milton Bradley & Co. April 30, 1914 2
Unidentified April 30, 1914 2
Unidentified April 30, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. May 15, 1914 2
Greene, Frederick R. May 15, 1914 2
LeGarde, Ellen May 15, 1914 2
Talbot, Mrs. C.H. May 5, 1914 2
G.E. Stechert & Co. May 18, 1914 2
Feagin, William F. May 21, 1914 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown May 25, 1914 2
Freen, Frederick R. May 25, 1914 2
Johnson, R.R. May 25, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. May 25, 1914 2
McBrien, J.M. May 25, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. May 25, 1914 2
Goldsberry, L.D. May 29, 1914 2
Green, Frederick R. May 29, 1914 2
Oliver C. Steele Mfg. Co. June 4, 1914 2
Commissioner of Education June 30, 1914 2
Feagin, William F. June 30, 1914 2
Ryan, Dr. June 30, 1914 2
Ryan, Dr. July 1, 1914 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown July 10, 1914 2
LaGarde, Ellen July 10, 1914 2
Schreuder, A.J. July 10, 1914 2
Story, Thomas A. July 10, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. July 16, 1914 2
Cheney, C.H. July 18, 1914 2
Haddon, R.W. July 18, 1914 2
Ittner, W.B. July 18, 1914 2
Naramore, F.A. July 18, 1914 2
Packard, F.L. July 18, 1914 2
Talbott, Mrs. C.H. July 18, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Aug. 4, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Aug. 24, 1914 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. Aug. 24, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Aug. 24, 1914 2
Nixon, M.F. Aug. 24, 1914 2
Storey, Thomas A. Aug. 24, 1914 2
Wilson, Louis N. Aug. 27, 1914 2
Naramore, NFN Sept. 2, 1914 2
McBrien, J.S. Sept. 12, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 17, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Sept. 17, 1914 2
Cheney, Charles H. Oct. 1, 1914 2
Monroe, Paul Oct. 1, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Oct. 1, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Oct. 6, 1914 2
Feagin, W.F. Oct. 6, 1914 2
Hatch, Wallace Oct. 6, 1914 2
McBrien, J.L. Oct. 6, 1914 2
Carroll, James E. Oct. 13, 1914 2
Hanson-Bellows Co. Oct. 13, 1914 2
Jones, Martha R. Oct. 13, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Oct. 13, 1914 2
Rider-Ericsson Engine Co. Oct. 13, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Oct. 17, 1914 2
Nicholson, M.M. Oct. 17, 1914 2
Nelson, A.H. Oct. 20, 1914 2
Putnam, Dana G. Oct. 20, 1914 2
Ferrell, John A. Oct. 23, 1914 2
Beers, Clifford W. Oct. 26, 1914 2
LeGarde, Ellen Oct. 30, 1914 2
Rasor, Alpha Oct. 31, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 4, 1914 2
Nelson, A.H. Nov. 4, 1914 2
Roach, Walter W. Nov. 4, 1914 2
Wray, George B. Nov. 4, 1914 2
Beers, Clifford W. Nov. 5, 1914 2
Payne, Dr. Nov. 5, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 7, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 10, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson Nov. 10, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 12, 1914 2
Lee, R.E. Nov. 12, 1914 2
Wray, George B. Nov. 12, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 17, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman Nov. 17, 1914 2
Lee, R.E. Nov. 17, 1914 2
Miller, A. E. Nov. 17, 1914 2
Cobb, H.A. Nov. 24, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 24, 1914 2
Belcher A. Dec. 1, 1914 2
Ittner, William B. Dec. 3, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Dec. 3, 1914 2
Moultrop, S. Dec. 3, 1914 2
Portis, R. Rivers Dec. 3, 1914 2
Blue, Rupert Dec. 5, 1914 2
Bronson, Charles A. Dec. 8, 1914 2
Burnham, W.H. Dec. 8, 1914 2
Palmer, T.W. Dec. 8, 1914 2
Cheney, Charles H. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Corwin, R.W. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Green, Frederick C. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Hacker, W.A. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Steele, William L. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 10, 1914 2
Blue, Rupert Dec. 15, 1914 2
Palmer, T.W. Dec. 15, 1914 2
Howell, Harry Dec. 17, 1914 2
Palmer, Thomas W. Dec. 17, 1914 2
Rasor, Alpha Dec. 17, 1914 2
Bruce, William C. Dec. 19, 1914 2
Hatfield, Frank H. Dec. 19, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Dec. 19, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. Dec. 22, 1914 2
Kingsley, Mr. Dec. 26, 1914 2
Putnam, D.G. Dec. 30, 1914 2
Blue, Rupert C. Dec. 31, 1914 2
Franklin, W.S. Dec. 31, 1914 2
Putnam, Dana G. Dec. 31, 1914 2
Stiles, O.W. Dec. 31, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. 1914, undated 2
Ferrell, John A. Jan. 5, 1915 2
Kellogg, Fanny Jan. 5, 1915 2
Linn, W.B. Jan. 9, 1915 2
Wray, George B. Jan. 9, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 16, 1915 2
Patterson, Thomas H. Jan. 16, 1915 2
Wood, Thomas D. Jan. 16, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 20, 1915 2
Dixon, Samuel G. Jan. 21, 1915 2
Goddard, Henry H. Jan. 21, 1915 2
Meier, Henry Jan. 21, 1915 2
Reiche, Karl A. Jan. 21, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 22, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 22, 1915 2
Kinnaman, A.J. Jan. 22, 1915 2
Wray, George B. Jan. 22, 1915 2
Burbank, S.M. Jan. 26, 1915 2
Charles Scribner & Sons Jan. 26, 1915 2
Kinnaman, A.J. Jan. 26, 1915 2
Martin, Mrs. Atwood R. Jan. 26, 1915 2
Roemer, O.P. Jan. 26, 1915 2
Taylor, H.L. Jan. 26, 1915 2
Claxton. P.P. Feb. 3, 1915 2
Franklin, W.S. Feb. 3, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 3, 1915 2
Palmer, T.W. Feb. 3, 1915 2
Roemer, T.P. Feb. 4, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 6, 1915 2
Abercrombie, John Feb. 9, 1915 2
Challman, S.A. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Chamberlain, A.H. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Johnson, George E. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 9, 1915 2
McElhaney, Ethel F. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Odum, Howard Feb. 9, 1915 2
Storey, T.E. Feb. 9, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 13, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. Feb. 13, 1915 2
Broady, Nancy Lee Feb. 16, 1915 2
Guilbert & Betelle, Architects Feb. 16, 1915 2
Kinnaman, A.J. Feb. 16, 1915 2
Odum, Howard W. Feb. 16, 1915 2
Wynn, W. Feb. 16, 1915 2
Storey, Thomas A. Feb. 18, 1915 2
Story, T.E. Feb. 18, 1915 2
Johnson, R.C. Feb. 19, 1915 2
Hillis, Edith Feb. 20, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 20, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. Feb. 20, 1915 2
McElhaney, Ethel F. Feb. 20, 1915 2
Church, A.K. Feb. 24, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 24, 1915 2
F.A. Davis & Co. Feb. 24, 1915 2
Jones, Addison L. Feb. 24, 1915 2
Storey, Thomas A. Feb. 24, 1915 2
Bowers, John H. Feb. 25, 1915 2
Challman, S.A. Feb. 25, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. Feb. 25, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. Feb. 25, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Feb. 25, 1915 2
LeGarde, Ellen Feb. 25, 1915 2
Lindsley, Louise G. Feb. 25, 1915 2
Perkins, Fellows & Hamilton Feb. 25, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson Feb. 25, 1915 2
Storey, Thomas A. Feb. 25, 1915
Johnston, R.C. Feb. 26, 1915 2
Kinnaman, A.J. Feb. 26, 1915 2
Putnam, D.G. Feb. 26, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. Feb. 27, 1915 2
Hutchens, W.T. Feb. 27, 1915 2
Journal Boston Society Medical Feb. 27, 1915 2
Love, Edgar L. Feb. 27, 1915 2
Wallis, R.C. Feb. 27, 1915 2
Dodson, John M. March 1, 1915 2
Johnston, R.C. March 1, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. March 1, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. March 1, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. March 1, 1915 2
Lathrop, Julia C. March 1, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. March 1, 1915 2
Roemer, O.P. March 1, 1915 2
Skidmore, C.H. March 1, 1915 2
Wallis, R.C. March 1, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. March 2, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 2, 1915 2
Wolcott, John D. March 2, 1915 2
Crozier, N.R. March 3, 1915 2
Johnston, R.C. March 3, 1915 2
Morgenthaler, F.S. March 3, 1915 2
Rice Hotel March 3, 1915 2
Wolcott, John D. March 3, 1915 2
Adcock, J.A.B. March 4, 1915 2
Bracken, H.M. March 4, 1915 2
Burkart, John L. March 4, 1915 2
Carr, E. Arthur March 4, 1915 2
Cosswell, W.F. March 4, 1915 2
Grumbine, S.J. March 4, 1915 2
Currie, Donald H. March 4, 1915 2
Dowling, Oscar March 4, 1915 2
Drake, C. St. Clair March 4, 1915 2
Falk, Ralph March 4, 1915 2
Frantz, A.E. March 4, 1915 2
Fulton, John S. March 4, 1915 2
Galloway, E.H. March 4, 1915 2
Harris, H.F. March 4, 1915 2
Hunter, Pauli S. March 4, 1915 2
Hurty, J.N. March 4, 1915 2
Lee, S.L. March 4, 1915 2
Looney, Robert N. March 4, 1915 2
McCormack, A.T. March 4, 1915 2
Porter, Joseph Y. March 4, 1915 2
Porter, K.B. March 4, 1915 2
Richardson, Mark W. March 4, 1915 2
Sanders, W.H. March 4, 1915 2
Smith, Morgan March 4, 1915 2
Sumner, Guilford H. March 4, 1915 2
Townsend, Joseph H. March 4, 1915 2
Watson, Irving A. March 4, 1915 2
Woodward, William C. March 4, 1915 2
Beatty, T.B. March 5, 1915 2
Biggs, Herman M. March 5, 1915 2
Dalton, Charles F. March 5, 1915 2
Dixon, Samuel G. March 5, 1915 2
Harper, C.A. March 5, 1915 2
Hayne, James A. March 5, 1915 2
Heiser, Victor G. March 5, 1915 2
Jepson, S.L. March 5, 1915 2
Kelley, Eugene R. March 5, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 5, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 5, 1915 2
Lillard, R.Q. March 5, 1915 2
Lippitt, William F. March 5, 1915 2
McCampbell, E.F. March 5, 1915 2
McGurren, J.M. March 5, 1915 2
Mahr, J.C. March 5, 1915 2
Price, Jacob C. March 5, 1915 2
Rankin, W.S. March 5, 1915 2
Steiner, Ralph March 5, 1915 2
Swarts, Gardner T. March 5, 1915 2
White, Calvin S. March 5, 1915 2
Williams, Ennion G. March 5, 1915 2
Snow, William F. March 7, 1915 2
Brooks, Frankie March 8, 1915 2
Corwin, R.W. March 8, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. March 8, 1915 2
Ittner, William B. March 8, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. March 8, 1915 2
Lee, Frederick S. March 8, 1915 2
LeGarde, Ellen March 8, 1915 2
Matthews, Homer D. March 8, 1915 2
Robertson, A.T. March 8, 1915 2
Smith, C.O. March 8, 1915 2
Terman, Lewis M. March 8, 1915 2
Woolcott, John D. March 8, 1915 2
Broady, Nancy L. March 10, 191 2
Crampton, C. Ward March 10, 191 2
Goin, J.M. March 10, 191 2
Hyde, Blanche E. March 10, 191 2
DeLozier, A.O. March 11, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 11, 191 2
McCulloch, J.E. March 11, 191 2
Myers, Winter W. March 11, 191 2
NY State Cmsn. on Ventilation March 11, 191 2
Wolcott, John D. March 11, 191 2
Binkhart, John L. March 12, 191 2
Grumbine, S.J. March 12, 191 2
Ennis, Robert Berry March 12, 191 2
Fulton, John S. March 12, 191 2
Galloway, E.H. March 12, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 12, 191 2
McCormack, A.T. March 12, 191 2
Porter, Joseph Y. March 12, 191 2
Sumner, Guilford H. March 12, 191 2
Bracken, H.M. March 13, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 13, 191 2
Skidmore, V.M. March 13, 191 2
Woodward, William C. March 13, 191 2
Cogswell, W.F. March 15, 191 2
Dalton, Charles F. March 15, 191 2
Dixon, Samuel G. March 15, 191 2
Dowling, Oscar March 15, 191 2
Hutschcroft, L.W. March 15, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 15, 191 2
McGurren, C.J. March 15, 191 2
Mclaughlin, A.J. March 15, 191 2
Williams, Ennion G. March 15, 191 2
Arvold, A.G. March 16, 191 2
Bracken, H.M. March 16, 191 2
Drake, C. St. Clair March 16, 191 2
State Board of Health, Alabam March 16, 191 2
Ittner, William B. March 17, 191 2
Ennis, Robert Mary March 18, 191 2
Falk, Ralph March 18, 191 2
Gilbert & Betelle, Architects March 18, 191 2
Green, Frederick R. March 18, 191 2
Hurty, J.N. March 18, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 18, 191 2
Morgenthaler, F.S. March 18, 191 2
Wheeler, Forrest March 18, 191 2
Beatty, T.B. March 19, 191 2
Buerk, A.J. March 19, 191 2
Harrison, Katie Belle March 19, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 18, 191 2
Biggs, Hermann M. March 20, 191 2
Moore, E.H. March 20, 191 2
White, Calvin S. March 20, 191 2
Hunter, Pauli S. March 22, 191 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown March 23, 191 2
Myers Winter W. March 25, 191 2
Booker, Warren H. March 26, 191 2
Brown, J.B. March 26, 191 2
Claxton, P.P. March 26, 191 2
Haskins, C.A. March 26, 191 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. March 26, 191 2
Maphis, Charles G. March 26, 191 2
Naramore, F.A March 26, 191 2
Cramton, C. Ward March 29, 191 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown March 29, 191 2
Narmamore, F.A. March 29, 191 2
Price, Jacob C. March 29, 191 2
Story, T.E. March 29, 191 2
Ellis, Mabel Brown March 30, 191 2
Brooks, Frankie March 30, 191 2
Church, A.K. March 31, 191 2
Gulick, Julia March 31, 191 2
Hatfield, Frank March 31, 191 2
O’Donnell, T.C. March 31, 191 2
Martindale, Henrietta March 31, 191 2
Steadwell, B.S. March 31, 191 2
Wheeler, Forrest March 31, 191 2
Austral Window Co. April 1, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. April 1, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. April 1, 1915 2
Snow, W.F. April 1, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. April 2, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. April 3, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. April 5, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. AprilS, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. April S, 1915 2
Johnson, B.D. AprilS, 1915 2
Johnson, B.D. AprilS, 1915 2
Storey, T.E. AprilS, 1915 2
Franklin, W.S. April 9, 1915 2
Pettus, T.V. April 9, 1915 2
Tyson, W.E. April 9, 1915 2
Arvold, A.G. April 10, 1915 2
Grumbine, J.C. April 10, 1915 2
Ellis, Mabie Brown April 10, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank April 10, 1915 2
Philips, C.V. April 10, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. April 10, 1915 2
Wiles, E.P. April 10, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. April 13, 1915 2
Green, Frederick R. April 13, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. April 13, 1915 2
Jackson, Isabel April 13, 1915 2
Moulthrop, S.P. April 13, 1915 2
Small, Willard S. April 13, 1915 2
Wilkerson, R.E. April 13, 1915 2
Payne, Dr. April 14, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 17, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 19, 1915 2
Marsh, J.F. April 20, 1915 2
Hatfield, Frank H. April 21, 1915 2
Hines, L.N. April 21, 1915 2
Miller, James Alex April 21, 1915 2
Rye, Tom C. April 21, 1915 2
Small, W.S. April 21, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. April 26, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 26, 1915 2
Marsh, J.F. April 26, 1915 2
Blue, Rupert April 28, 1915 2
Bruce, William C. April 28, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. April 28, 1915 2
Pearse, Carroll G. April 28, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. April 28, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. April 28, 1915 2
Self, J.C. April 28, 1915 2
Shepherd, John W. April 28, 1915 2
Bancroft, Jessie H. April 29, 1915 2
Barnes, C.H. April 29, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. May 1, 1915 2
Cubberly, Elwood P. May 1, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. May 1, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. May 1, 1915 2
Donovan, John J. May 3, 1915 2
Roach, R.P. May 3, 1915 2
Adcock, Sam Y. May 4, 1915 2
Ayres, Leonard P. May 4, 1915 2
Church, H.V. May 4, 1915 2
Delozier, A.O. May 4, 1915 2
Keene, C.H. May 4, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. May 4, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. May 4, 1915 2
Small, W.S. May 4, 1915 2
Wolcott, J.D. May 4, 1915 2
Lund, Haviland H. May 5, 1915 2
NY State Cmsn. on Ventilation May 5, 1915 2
Jenks, C.L. May 6, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. MayS, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. May 6, 1915 2
Mathews, G.S. May 6, 1915 2
Roach, R.P. May 6, 1915 2
Wolcott, John D. May 6, 1915 2
Barnes, C.H. May 8, 1915 2
Langslow, H.R. May 8, 1915 2
Small, W.S. MayS, 1915 2
Bancroft, Jesse H. May 11, 1915 2
Brooks, Frankie May 12, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. May 15, 1915 2
Reed, C.E. May 15, 1915 2
Roach, R.P. May 15, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. May 17, 1915 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. May 17, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. May 17, 1915 2
Andress, J. Mace May 18, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. May 18, 1915 2
Lund, Haviland H. May 18, 1915 2
Wolcott, John D. May 18, 1915 2
Wood, Thomas D. May 18, 1915 2
Barthram, Frank M. May 21, 1915 2
McTate, Jannie F. May 21, 1915 2
Hartwell, Harry T. May 22, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. May 24, 1915 2
Wolcott, J.D. May 24, 1915 2
Adcock, Sam Y. May 26, 1915 2
Wiggers, J.A. May 27, 1915 2
Hall-Quest, Alfred L. May 28, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. May 28, 1915 2
Bancroft, Jesse H. June 1, 1915 2
Bartram, Frank M. June 1, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. June 1, 1915 2
Daman, E.O., Jr. June 1, 1915 2
Fowler Langslow Co. June 1, 1915 2
Healy, Thomas D. June 1, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. June 1, 1915 2
McTate, Jannie F. June 1, 1915 2
G. E. Stechert & Co. June 2, 1915 2
Wolcott, John D. June 2, 1915 2
Andress, J. Mace June 3, 1915 2
Barnes, C.H. June 3, 1915 2
Donovan, John J. June 3, 1915 2
Mathews, Gertrude June 3, 1915 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 4, 1915 2
Healy, Mary L. June 4, 1915 2
Ittner, William B. June 4, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. June 4, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. June 4, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. June 4, 1915 2
Wiggers, J.A. June 4, 1915 2
Wood, Thomas D. June 4, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. June 7, 1915 2
Mayers, David Campbell June?, 1915 2
Sturgis & Walton Co. June 7, 1915 2
Healy, Thomas D. June 9, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. June 9, 1915 2
Foster, James H. June 11, 1915 2
Morelock, G.L. June 11, 1915 2
Andress, J. Mace June 14, 1915 2
Foster, James H. June 11, 1195 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. June 14, 1915 2
Payne, Bruce R. June 14, 1915 2
Stephen, James June 14, 1915 2
Hartwell, Harry T. June 15, 1915 2
Cherry, H.H. June 21, 1915 2
Diii,J.W. June 21, 1915 2
Donovan, Jonathan J. June 21, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. June 21, 1915 2
Langslow, H.R. June 21, 1915 2
Roach, R.P. June 21, 1915 2
Feminear, Mary June 23, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. June 26, 1915 2
Hartwell, Harry T. June 26, 1915 2
Martin, Leon A. June 26, 1915 2
Hartwell, Harry T. June 29, 1915 2
LeGarde, Ellen June 29, 1915 2
Leathers, W.S. June 30, 1915 2
Lund, Haviland H. June 30, 1915 2
Luther, Agnes Vinton June 21, 1915 2
Macmillan Co. June 21, 1915 2
Schapiro, Louis June 21, 1915 2
Funderburk, Martha July 5, 1915 2
University of Georgia July 5, 1915 2
Pratt, Thomas P. July 7, 1915 2
Martin, Leon A. July 8, 1915 2
Van Duzor, Charlotte E. July 8, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. July 16, 1915 2
Cook, Grant July 16, 1915 2
Finley, John L. July 16, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. July 16, 1915 2
LeGarde, Ellen July 16, 1915 2
Smith, Austin W. July 16, 1915 2
Corwin, R.W. July 19, 1915 2
Manning, Frank A. July 19, 1915 2
Nunn, Roscoe July 19, 1915 2
Small, W.S. July 19, 1915 2
Smith, Austin W. July 19, 1915 2
Ryan, W. Carson July 23, 1915 2
Smith, Austin W. July 23, 1915 2
Turlington, Ira T. July 23, 1915 2
Smith, Austin W. July 27, 1915 2
Colebanks, C.H. July 31, 1915 2
Smith, Austin W. July 31, 1915 2
Stuaart, M.H. July 31, 1915 2
Ballard, S. Thruston Oct. 13, 1915 2
Barker, Blanche Wiggin Oct. 13, 1195 2
Claxton, P.P. Oct. 13, 1915 2
Harmon, J.C. Oct. 13, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Oct. 13, 1915 2
Wright, Robert H. Oct. 13, 1915 2
Battson, J.M. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Bennett, L.E. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Broaddus, Mrs. H. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Monroe, Robert C. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Morris, Frank A. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Purdam, B.K. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Rapeer, Louis W. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Shaw, John C. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Sugg, H.B. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Wray, Joe S. Oct. 14, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Oct. 19, 1915 2
J.H. Felt & Co. Oct. 19, 1915 2
Kalbach, L.A. Oct. 19, 1915 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Oct. 191, 195 2
Wood, Thomas D. Oct. 19, 1915 2
Andress, J. Mace Oct. 21, 1915 2
McLeskey, W.B. Nov. 2, 1915 2
Gayle, E.F. Nov. 3, 1915 2
Johnson, Axel Nov. 3, 1915 2
Ballard, S. Thurston Nov. 4, 1915 2
Bishop, Fred G. Dec. 2, 1915 2
Howell, Harry Dec. 2, 1915 2
McCulloch, J.E. Dec. 2, 1915 2
Shawkey, M.P. Dec. 2, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 3, 1915 2
Linn, W.B. Dec. 3, 1915 2
Walker, Lula Dec. 3, 1915 2
Wright, Robert H. Dec. 3, 1195 2
Ittner, W.B. Dec. 9, 1915 2
Purdum, B.K. Dec. 9, 1915 2
Johnson, Judson Dec. 13, 1915 2
Rudd, Channing Dec. 13, 1915 2
Donald, James T. Dec. 16, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 21, 1915 2
Lund, Haviland H. Dec. 22, 1915 2
Smith, A.J. Dec. 22, 1915 2
Shackelford, Mr. Dec. 23, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 27, 1915 2
Claxton, P.P. 1915, undated 2
King, Jeannette M. 1915, undated 2
Manley, Ida M. 1915, undated 2
Pace, Johnson, H. 1915, undated 2
Peelle, Stanton J. Jan. 6, 1916 2
Barnes, F.B. Jan. 10, 1916 2
Hatcher, J.F. Jan. 13, 1916 2
Diffenbaugh, Mr. Jan. 14, 1916 2
Kinsley, NFN Jan. 17, 1916 2
Hatcher, J.F. Jan. 24, 1916 2
King, Miss Jan. 24, 1916 2
Minnich, O.C. Jan. 24, 1916 2
Hackett, Frank S. Jan. 25, 1916 2
Barnes, John G. Jan. 27, 1916 2
Hankins, W.O. Jan. 27, 1916 2
Peele, Stanton J. Jan. 27, 1916 2
Sense, Mr. Jan. 27, 1916 2
McDougle, E.C. Jan. 29, 1916 2
Murphy, Mr. Feb. 10, 1916 2
Moore, J. Alex March 4, 1916 2
Galbreath, President March 6, 1916 2
Moore, J. Alex March 6, 1916 2
Putnam, Helen G. March 7, 1916 2
Hall, F.M. March 8, 1916 2
Heald, Arthur A. March 8, 1916 2
March, William H. March 8, 1916 2
Muller, Herman March 8, 1916 2
Putnam, Helen G. March 8, 1916 2
Rich, Ednah A. March 8, 1916 2
Sheldon, Dr. March 8, 1916 2
Billie, Edward Fournier March 9, 1916 2
Perrine, C.H. March 9, 1916 2
Tenney, Ross L. March 9, 1916 2
Suhrie, Ambrose L. March 10, 191 2
Lund, Haviland H. March 14, 191 2
Moore, J. Alex March 15, 191 2
Moore, J. Alex March 15, 191 2
Diegaard & Rinding March 16, 191 2
Guss, Margaret March 16, 191 2
Haynes, Barney S. March 16, 191 2
Bancroft, Jessie H. March 24, 191 2
Howell, Harry March 24, 191 2
Moore, J. Alex March 24, 191 2
Neimchesky, L.J. March 24, 191 2
Norton, H.B. March 24, 191 2
Robinson, W.G. March 24, 191 2
Samuelson, Agnes March 27, 191 2
Wardlaw, J.C. March 28, 191 2
Douglas, A.E. March 30, 191 2
Moore, Mr. March 30, 191 2
Stewart March 30, 191 2
Burkes, Jennie April 8, 1916 2
Keith, C.A. April 8, 1916 2
Bain, Samuel M. April 11, 1916 2
Montandon, Charles A. April 11, 1916 2
Moore, J. Alex April 11, 1916 2
Ryan, W. Carson April 11, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. April 12, 1916 2
Barnes, John G. April 18, 1916 2
McMillan, Henry April 18, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. April 18, 1916 2
Webb, Susana April 18, 1916
Hatfield, Frank H. April 24, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. April 24, 1916 2
Wood, Thomas D. April 24, 1916
Graves, T.D. April 25, 1916 2
McNutty, T.E. April 25, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. April 25, 1916 2
Washburn, J.L. April 25, 1916 2
Welton, William Lesley April 25, 1916 2
Rapp, E.M. April 27, 1916 2
Hatfield, Frank H. April 29, 1916 2
McLure, John R. April 29, 1916 2
Rudd, Channing April 29, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. April 29, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. May 3, 1916 2
Claxton, P.P. May 11, 1916 2
Henry, D.R. May 11, 1916 2
McLain, Mr. May 11, 1916 2
Phillips, C.A. May 11, 1916 2
Putnam, Herbert L. May 11, 1916 2
Ranck, F.E. May 11, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. May 11, 1916 2
Cassell, R.B. May 13, 1916 2
Foght, Harold W. May 18, 1916 2
Green, L.E. May 22, 1916 2
McCulley, Ruth A. May 22, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. May 22, 1916 2
Wardlaw, Mr. May 26, 1916 2
Dadisman, S.H. May 30, 1916 2
Gauntt, James G. May 30, 1916 2
Harrison, NFN May 30, 1916 2
Lewis, E.M. May 31, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. May 31, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. June 6, 1916 2
Stewart June 7, 1916 2
Hollis, S.P. June 13, 1916 2
Keithly, E.W. June 13, 1916 2
Wardlaw, J.C. June 13, 1916 2
Milligan, R.M. July 1, 1916 2
Johnston, Helen July 5, 1916 2
Claxton, P.P. July 18, 1916 2
Monee, U.L. July 31, 1916 2
Hamilton, Carline M. Aug. 1, 1916 2
Nichols, Mr. Aug. 1, 1916 2
Baker, N.R. Aug. 10, 1916 2
Moore, J. Alex Aug 10, 1916 2
Stewart, Alexander T. Aug. 10, 1916 2
Traweek, P.B. Aug. 10, 1916 2
Talbott, W.R. Aug. 19, 1916 2
Howey, E.W. Aug. 21, 1916 2
Price, Warren Aug. 26, 1916 2
Gilbert, Mr. Aug. 26, 1916 2
Ellis, A. Caswell Aug. 28, 1916 2
Copeland, Ada B. Aug. 31, 1916 2
Barefield, M.D. Sept. 24, 1916 2
Miller, Charles E. Sept. 24, 1916 2
Ratliff, F.C. Sept. 29, 1916 2
Dunaway, Mr. Oct. 9, 1916 2
Dunn, W.W. Oct. 9, 1916 2
Moore, I.P. Oct. 9, 1916 2
Talbott, W.R. Oct. 14, 1916 2
Payne, Dr. Oct. 18, 1916 2
Kingsley, NFN Oct. 22, 1916 2
Wood, Frank H. Oct. 22, 1916 2
Payne, Dr. Oct. 31, 1916 2
Dunnaway, O.L. Nov. 1, 1916 2
Henderson, M.T. Nov. 4, 1916 2
Muerman, Dr. Nov. 4, 1916 2
Varney, Penn Nov. 4, 1916 2
Wood, Dr. Nov. 4, 1916 2
Groos, Alfred W. Nov. 6, 1916 2
Rule, Lillian Nov. 6, 1916 2
Sullivan, Louis H. Nov. 6, 1916 2
McKenzie, F.A. Nov. 7, 1916 2
Watkins, W.H. Nov. 9, 1916 2
Wilkinson, W.A. Nov. 9, 1916 2
Dunaway, O.L. Nov. 13, 1916 2
Spencer, Raymond B. Dec. 11, 1916 2
Bancroft, Jessie H. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Budd, Nora Dec. 18, 1916 2
Edwards, Frank L. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Kind, Grace Dec. 18, 1916 2
Latham, R.H. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Lund, Haviland H. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Moore, J.A. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Swarts, Gardner T., Jr. Dec. 18, 1916 2
Ray, S.W. Dec. 20, 1916 2
Payne, Bruce R. Dec. 29, 1916 2
Ramsey, H.D. 1916, undated 2
Dreisbach, J.F. Jan. 1, 1917 2
Dunaway, O.L. Jan. 8, 1917 2
Dunaway, O.L. Jan. 9, 1917 2
Dunaway, O.L. Jan. 12, 1917 2